<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Awayto</title>
    <link>https://wcapp.site.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Awayto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wcapp.site.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://wcapp.site.com/posts/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wcapp.site.com/posts/faq/</guid>
      <description>If you feel that this list doesn&amp;rsquo;t answer your questions, please join the discord to suggest changes.
What gets installed? You can review the old installation guide to get an idea of the more detailed changes the installation process applies to AWS. In general, after running the installer, the following resources will be deployed to AWS:
Cognito User Pool Cognito App Client RDS Postgres Instance (t3.micro) API Gateway stage containing authorized and unauthorized routes Lambda Function to receive gateway events Service worker &amp;lsquo;LambdaTrust&amp;rsquo; role for lambda-service group access S3 buckets for hosting built web and API bundles CloudFormation distribution to serve the webapp from S3 Local file system containing a generic Lambda node-based API, Typescript type suite, and React web app originally generated with create-react-app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://wcapp.site.com/posts/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wcapp.site.com/posts/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites AWS Administrator with AWS CLI (2.0.42) Python (3.7.9) Postgres (13.4) NodeJS (16.3.0) NPM (7.15.1) Docker (4.3; for SAM Local testing) Installation Awayto installs as a global npm package because you will use it to deploy entire file structures for your application or API.
npm i -g @keybittech/awayto
With the CLI installed, you can go into any folder and install a new project with Awayto!
install &amp;ndash; awayto install &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;environment&amp;gt; &amp;quot;&amp;lt;description&amp;gt;&amp;quot; This will install Awayto into the current directory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
